<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Day24(Recycler View)</string>
    <string name="news0">MI vs CSK Highlights, IPL 2023: Rahane, Jadeja lead Chennai Super Kings to 7-wicket victory vs Mumbai Indians</string>
    <string name="mi_vs_csk_highlights_ipl_2023_csk_get_7_wicket_victory_vs_mi">MI vs CSK Highlights, IPL 2023: CSK get 7-wicket victory vs MI</string>
    <string name="image">Image</string>

    <string name="news1">IPL 2023 MI vs CSK preview:
        The stage is set for the Indian Premier League’s version of the ‘El Clasico’
        with Mumbai Indians (MI) taking on Chennai Super Kings (CSK) in Mumbai’s Wankhede
        Stadium in the second game of the Saturday double-header. IPL 2023: Full coverage
        | Points table | Schedule | Results | Orange Cap | Purple Cap MI and CSK are two of the most decorated teams
        in the history of the Indian Premier League with nine titles between them, five of which have been won by Mumbai
        under Rohit Sharma’s leadership. Dhoni, who led Chennai to a runner-up finish in the inaugural edition in 2008 and
        would go on to win four titles with the ‘Yellow Army’ — the last of which came in 2021, will be hoping to go level
        with CSK’s eternal rivals in what could be his final season as a player. MI and CSK have also squared off in the final
        more than any other team — the two sides have met in four finals (2010, 2013, 2015 and 2019), with Mumbai finishing
        runners-up in 2010 under Sachin Tendulkar’s leadership and winning the remaining ones under Rohit. As for the current
        season, Mumbai are among the handful of sides who are yet to win a game, having been steamrolled by Royal Challengers
        Bangalore (RCB) by eight wickets in their opening game at Bengaluru’s M Chinnaswamy Stadium. Chennai, on the other hand,
        bounced back from a defeat against Gujarat Titans in the season opener with a 12-run win over Lucknow Super Giants (LSG)
        — in their first match in Chepauk since 2019 — on Monday.
        Teams: Chennai Super Kings: Devon Conway, Ruturaj Gaikwad, Ajinkya Rahane, Ravindra Jadeja, MS Dhoni(w/c), Shivam Dube,
        Dwaine Pretorius, Deepak Chahar, Mitchell Santner, Sisanda Magala, Tushar Deshpande
        Mumbai Indians: Rohit Sharma©, Ishan Kishan(w), Cameron Green, Suryakumar Yadav, Tilak Varma, Tim David, Tristan Stubbs, Arshad Khan,
        Hrithik Shokeen, Piyush Chawla, Jason Behrendorff</string>

</resources>